# Mr. Anuchit Nootjanya

61/49 Lumlukka Kukot Pathumtani 12130, +66 84 902 7007 anuchit.noo@outlook.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/ANootjanya

## IT Business Analyst and Software Engineer

IT Project Management, Design and Development, Business and System Analysis,



Determined, responsible, and committed with a good attitude. Experience in analysis, design high level solution and design in detail, and implementing web application with Java technology based on application Life-Cycle management. Co-ordinated, collaborated, and consolidated in order to get it done within timeline.

#### Personal Details

• Age: 36

• Date of Birth: July 27, 1980

• Gender: Male

• Height and Weight: 176 Centimeters/ 70 Kilograms

Nationality: ThaiReligion: BuddhismMarital Status: Single

#### Technical Skills

Languages: Java, JSP, Java Script, HTML
Operating Systems: Windows, Unix

• Database: Oracle, SQL, DB2

### **Education & Certifications**

Thammasat University – Bangkok Thailand Master Degree in College of Innovation, August 2011,GPA 3.55

The University of the Thai Chamber of Commerce – Bangkok Thailand Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, November 2004, GPA 2.54

### Professional Experience

Software Engineer and IT Business Analyst, September 2011 to Present – United Overseas Bank Thailand, Bangkok, Thailand

### Responsibility

- Provided IT solutions as an IT business analyst and development according to business requirements in part of personal internet banking and business internet banking.
- Coordinate business users, operation users, and relevant IT team in part of internet banking channel.
- Provided programming both web application and related back-end system.
- Support IT internal request such as regression testing, disaster recovery plan, and IT audit.
- Production support and finding work around for interim solution in part of internet banking channels.

Contact vendors and recruitment outsourcing.

### Major Project Experienced

- Business Internet Banking Migration Project in 2016
- Mainframe Decommission Project in 2016
- Personal Internet Banking Migration Project in 2014
- Core Bank Migration Project in part of Personal Internet Banking and Business Internet Banking in 2011

# System Analyst, June 2007 to May 2011 – Advanced Info Service, Bangkok, Thailand Responsibility

- Provided programming support, user requirements analysis and design of Web application for AIS's internal users
- Proved of concepts in IT technologies and applying to AIS IT systems such as SOA improvement in AIS.
- Impact assessment, contributed in analysis and design high level solutions for new AIS new services.

#### Contributed Project

 Service Fulfilment project for support customer profile management and provisioning to relevant back-end systems.

# Java Web Developer, December 2004 to May 2007 – Soft Square 1999, Pathumtani, Thailand Responsibility

 Provided programming support of Java web application development and maintenance with Java programming on SPRING, STRUT, AJAX, and Hibernate Framework.

#### Contributed Project

- Standardize of Java web application.
- GEM TV Web application for selling jewelry and game.
- Thailand Post HR and internal information management.
- Department of Lands internal information management.

# Java Application Developer, August to November 2004 – Advanced Intelligence Modernity, Bangkok, Thailand

#### Responsibility

Provided programming support of Java application and development on Oracle.

#### Contributed Project

SET (Stock Exchange of Thailand) work flow management java application.

# Web Developer, November 2003 to June 2004 – Thomas Idea, Bangkok, Thailand Responsibility

 Contributed to web application development and maintenance by programming on Java, JSP, JavaScript, and ASP language with SQL server.

#### Contributed Project

 Suzuki dealer web application. Mahaphant's product management web application, and Karonna resort booking web application.